Guide to the Nelson Sullivan Video Collection 1976 - 1989 MSS 357
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Videorecordings, 1976 - 1988
  - Atlanta: Dick and Rupaul and Barker, February 8, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0410)
  - Grandmama’s in Kershaw with Jeanie and Ryan, News Era and Horses, February 3, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0411)
  - Wigstock Benefit (part 1), May 13, 1987 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0412)
  - Video Titles for Joey Arias by Nelson Sullivan, Dean Johnson and John Sex at Palladium, September 25, 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0413)
  - Celebrity Club (broken tape), June 29, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0414)
  - Dirt #2 at Limelight, November 3, 1987 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0415)
  - Atlanta #6, August 18, 1987 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0416)
  - Celebrity Club with Wendy Wild, May 18, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0417)
  - Pose Arena at Pyramid, Rooftop, East Village, June 25, 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0418)
    [1] -- Pose Arena at Pyramid, 6/25/1986 [2] -- Rooftop, East Village, 6/26/1986
  - Keita in NYC, March 16, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0419)
  - Downtown Recording Session at 1697 Broadway, April 16, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0420)
  - Hattie’s Birthday, Pyramid to Party, 70’s Party at Tunnel, March 1987 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0421)
    [1] -- Hattie’s Birthday, Pyramid to Party, 3/30/1987 [2] -- 70’s Party at Tunnel, 3/31/1987
  - Photo Session at Liz’s for Fenton’s “Queens” Article for Graffiti, April 20, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0422)
  - Celebrity Club, RuPaul Leaves for London, July 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0423)
    [1] -- Celebrity Club, 7/27/1988 [2] -- RuPaul Leaves for London, 7/31/1988
  - Christmas, Big Haus, Copa with Lady Hennessy, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0424)
    [1] -- Christmas, 12/25/1987 [2] -- Big Haus, 3/30/1989 [3] -- Copa with Lady Hennessy, 3/30/1989
  - Atlanta: RuPaul at Colorbox (2nd set), XTC party at Dick’s, February 10, 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0425)
  - Pyramid Birthday 7 (tape #2), December 10, 1988 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0426)
  - Mystery Girls, D. Leslie, Fred S., Christina, June 28, 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0427)
  - Atlanta #4 Judy Lahoma Lizette, Sailing in Provincetown, August 1986 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0428)
    [1] -- Judy Lahoma Lizette, 8/10/1986 [2] -- Sailing in Provincetown, 8/15/1986
  - Johnny Brewer, Last Day Home, Trip to Richards and to Atlanta, February 1989 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0429)
    [1] -- Johnny Brewer, Last Day Home, 2/5/1989 [2] -- Trip to Richards and to Atlanta, 2/6/1989
  - Fetchin Bones at CBGB's (part 1), Pyramid 6th Birthday (2 of 2), December 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0430)
    [1] -- Fetchin Bones at CBGB's (part 1), 12/8/1987 [2] -- Pyramid 6th Birthday (2 of 2), 12/10/1987
  - Julie Jewels Fashion Show, June 15, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0431)
  - Coney Island with Molli, Trade, Jon, RuPaul, Larry Tee, Rosser - Busted by the Pigs!, July 24, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0432)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid, Now Explosion at Pyramid, November 24, 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0433)
  - Christmas Eve with Betty Thom at Sylvia's, Christmas at Home, December 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0434)
    [1] -- Christmas Eve with Betty Thom at Sylvia's, 12/24/1987 [2] -- Christmas at Home, 12/25/1987
  - Atlanta #8 Nancy 1987, August 22, 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0435)
  - Michael Musto Birthday Bananas, Hope Nicholls & Fetchin Bones at Cat Club, December 7, 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0436)
  - Pyramid 6th Birthday (1 of 2), December 10, 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0437)
  - Michael London Benefit at Pyramid, June 3, 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0438)
  - La Palace at Red Zone, Bunny at Mars, Whispers at Paddles, April 16, 1989 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0439)
  - New Year’s Eve at Mars, Christina at 5 Ninth- Florent, Revelers, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0440)
    [1] -- New Year’s Eve at Mars, 12/31/1988 [2] -- Christina at 5 Ninth- Florent, 1/6/1989 [3] -- Revelers, 1/7/1989
  - Celebrity Club at Tunnel, June 1, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0441)
  - Pop Tarts Show, Nancy 1988, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0442)
    [1] -- Pop Tarts Show, 7/17/1988 [2] -- Nancy, 1988
  - July 4th, 1986 (part 1), July 4, 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0443)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger’s Rip Van Winkle, Hair (night #2) at The Saint, Pop Tarts limo, July 18, 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0444)
  - Starbooty and German Television, March 2, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0445)
  - Celebrity Club, Porn Rap Party, May 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0446)
    [1] -- Celebrity Club, 5/18/1988 [2] -- Porn Rap Party, 5/25/1988
  - World of Viola and $25,000 at Pyramid, La Palace at Pyramid, January 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0447)
    [1] -- World of Viola and $25,000 at Pyramid, 1/1/1988 [2] -- La Palace at Pyramid, 1/3/1988
  - Celebrity Club, Patrick, Fadia P. Michael Musto & More, July 27, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0448)
  - RuPaul May 22 & 23 at time of release party for Michael Musto’s book Downtown, May 22, 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0449)
  - Triple Birthday, Pop Tarts party at Tunnel with Albert, November 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0450)
    [1] -- Triple Birthday, 11/17/1987 [2] -- Pop Tarts party at Tunnel with Albert, 11/19/1987
  - Tish and Snooky with Dainty at Limelight, Continued: Eddie, Nick and Chica, December 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0451)
    [1] -- Tish and Snooky with Dainty at Limelight, 12/12/1986 [2] -- Continued: Eddie, Nick and Chica, 12/3/1986
  - Pop Tarts Party, Albert Crudo and his Pluto shorts, Drag Cat, Floyd's Party (part 2), December 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0452)
    [1] -- Pop Tarts Party, 12/13/1987 [2] -- Albert Crudo and his Pluto shorts, 12/13/1987 [3] -- Drag Cat, 12/15/1987 [4] -- Floyd's Party (part 2), 12/20/1987
  - Celebrity Cub #1, April 13, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0453)
  - Central Park with Blackout, Jon, Larry Tee, RuPaul, Trade, April 17, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0454)
  - Pop Tarts at The World, January 24, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0455)
  - Eric Conrad and Vicki at Trixie’s, January 7, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0456)
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid J continued, November 23, 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0457)
  - Julie Is Her Name at Pyramid (take one), February 1, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0458)
  - Craig Vandenberg and John Sex at Pyramid, January 10, 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0459)
  - Dean Johnson at Palladium, 2500 - Michael Musto Apartment (part 2), 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0460)
    [1] -- Dean Johnson at Palladium, 1/13/1987 [2] -- 2500 - Michael Musto Apartment (part 2), 1/27/1987
  - Information Society at 1018, Hanson Davis, November 7, 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0461)
  - Bitch Off at The World, May 27, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0462)
  - Paul Litteral & Karen Wedding, October 1, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0463)
  - Sylvia Miles at 19K, October 2, 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0464)
  - Wigstock #2 (part 2), September 1, 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0465)
  - Celebrity Club #2, Mykul Tronn Birthday, June 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0466)
    [1] -- Celebrity Club #2, 6/8/1988 [2] -- Mykul Tronn Birthday, 6/11/1988
  - Sylvia Miles in Tea with Mommy and Jack, undated (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0467)
  - Celebrity Club Funtone Night with Stephen Saban and The Singing Peek Sisters, July 20, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0468)
  - Joey Heatherrock, Tangella, Eddie, June 4, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0469)
  - Tish in East Village, Dinah Prince (master edit), June 2, 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0470)
  - Ethel Eichelberger in Klytemnestra, Thanksgiving, 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0471)
    [1] -- Ethel Eichelberger in Klytemnestra, 3/20/1987 [2] -- Thanksgiving, 11/23/1987
  - Fetchin Bones at CBGB’s (part 2), Pyramid to Home, La Palace at Siberia, December 1987 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0472)
    [1] -- Fetchin Bones at CBGB’s (part 2), 12/8/1987 [2] -- Pyramid to Home, 12/11/1987 [3] -- La Palace at Siberia, 12/12/1987
  - Sylvia Miles in Woodstock edit, Dominique at Liimelight (2800), September 10, 1986 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0473)
  - Celebrity Club with Diamanda Galas, August 3, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0474)
  - DV8 Roof Party, First Self Video, August 6, 1988 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0475)
  - Christina at The Chelsea, Jayne County at Pyramid, May 27, 1989 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0478)
  - Love Machine #1, June 27, 1989 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0479)
  - Chameleon Edit, December 8, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0480)
  - Amnesia at Gay Day Parade, June 25, 1989 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0481)
  - New Camera, Michael Alig Birthday, 1989 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0482)
  - Christina at Chelsea, 5 Ninth Avenue to Florent, Joey Heatherrock, Spank, 1989 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0483)
    [1] -- Christina at Chelsea, 5 Ninth Avenue to Florent, 3/28/1989 [2] -- Joey Heatherrock, Spank, 4/28/1989
  - RuPaul at Hairspray Party, February 22, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0484)
  - Monologue in Grenwich Village for First Cable Show, Bill Moye & Blackout at Pier (Nelson’s last tape), July 1989 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0485)
    [1] -- Monologue in Grenwich Village for First Cable Show, 7/2/1989 [2] -- Bill Moye & Blackout at Pier (Nelson’s last tape), 7/3/1989
  - Glen Meadmore at Pyramid, December 6, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0486)
  - RuPaul Pyramid Show, Grocery (crystal healing) (part2), November 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0487)
  - Lisa E in “Positive Me” #2, Floyd at Milk Bar, October 15, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0488)
  - Me and Eric in East Village, Gaylord at La Roca, June 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0489)
    [1] -- Me and Eric in East Village, 6/10/1987 [2] -- Gaylord at La Roca, 6/20/1987
  - John Sex at Limelight (small room), Specimen at Limelight (main room), Liberty with Tish and Gabriel, July 3, 1986 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0490)
  - Now Explosion at Limelight, May 15, 1986 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0491)
  - Atlanta 1987 #3, August 19, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0492)
  - Sea Cliff, New York, May 10, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0493)
  - Gullet without the G #1, September 18, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0494)
  - People Tree Siberia, People Tree at Pyramid, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0495)
    [1] -- People Tree Siberia, 10/6/1987 [2] -- People Tree at Pyramid, 1/17/1988
  - Walker Art Center at Easter, April 19, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0496)
  - Liz Party (part 2), Pop Tarts leave Liz’s, John Sex's birthday, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0497)
    [1] -- Liz Party (part 2), 3/29/1987 [2] -- Pop Tarts leave Liz’s, 4/11/1987 [3] -- John Sex's birthday, 4/11/1987
  - Limelight Wedding, September 7, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0498)
  - Rosie Rex at Pyramid, August 1, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0499)
  - Sunday, Trade, RuPaul head dress, Paris Band ICU, April 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0500)
    [1] -- Sunday, 4/10/1987 [2] -- Trade, RuPaul head dress, Paris Band ICU, 4/12/1987
  - Ballet of Dolls benefit #1 at Pyramid, October 8, 1986 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0501)
  - Paula’s Opening in San Francisco, Tour of the Inside of the DV8 Club, and Haight Asbury Visit at Floyd’s House where Jimmy Hendix and Janis Joplin lived and nearby acid party, February 14, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0502)
  - Continuation of April 1, 1988, La Palace at Pyramid, April 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0503)
    [1] -- Continuation of April 1, 1988, 4/1/1988 [2] -- La Palace at Pyramid, 4/2/1988
  - Pop Tarts Palladium Party, March 4, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0504)
  - DeeLite, John Sex, Wendy Wild at Pyramid, MTV at Tunnel, April 1, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0505)
  - New York to Atlanta, RuPaul at Weekends, Sunset, Alice Bost, Provincetown roof, George Johnson, August 1986 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0506)
    [1] -- New York to Atlanta, RuPaul at Weekends, 8/2/1986 [2] -- Sunset, Alice Bost, Provincetown roof, George Johnson, 8/16/1986
  - Nasomi and John, Flloyd’s party at Times Square, December 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0507)
    [1] -- Nasomi and John, 12/12/1987 [2] -- Flloyd’s party at Times Square, 12/20/1987
  - Albert to Pop Tarts to Limelight with Alexis and Karon, Dawn Huston, 1986 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0508)
    [1] -- Albert to Pop Tarts to Limelight with Alexis and Karon, 11/27/1987 [2] -- Dawn Huston, 12/7/1987
  - Michael Musto’s apartment and Trivia with Lisa, McA, James St. James (part 1), January 27, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0509)
  - Disco 88 at Pyramid, March 8, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0510)
  - My Birthday, March 15, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0511)
  - Celebrity Club, August 17, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0512)
  - Lady Clare in San Francisco, Walk in San Francisco, February 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0513)
    [1] -- Lady Clare in San Francisco, 2/14/1987 [2] -- Walk in San Francisco, 2/15/1987
  - Sunday with Lady Clare, Wigstock III (part 1), September 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0514)
    [1] -- Sunday with Lady Clare, 9/6/1987 [2] -- Wigstock III (part 1), 9/7/1987
  - Pyramid #2: Sister Dimension, John Kelly, Alexis, Michael London, Tom Rubnitz videos, Bunny, Mr. Fashion, October 8, 1986 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0515)
  - Apollo Mystery Concert 2 (part 2; speed edit), March 13, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0516)
  - Celebrity Club #4 at Tunnel, May 4, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0517)
  - Tunnel with John Sex, Alexis, Bunny, RuPaul, Craig Vandenberg, March 24, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0518)
  - Tony Cimino/Neil, June 4, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0519)
  - My Birthday (part 2 by Guy), Rhonda’s Birthday, March 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0520)
    [1] -- My Birthday (part 2 by Guy), 3/15/1987 [2] -- Rhonda’s Birthday, 3/21/1987
  - RuPaul Shows, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0521)
  - DV8 Trip to Boston (part 2), April 22, 1988 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0522)
  - Mystery Concert at Apollo Opera (6 singers), May 2, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0523)
  - Stas Namin at Limelight, October 9, 1986 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0524)
  - John Sex Birthday (part 2), A Coupla Vixens Talking, Albert in Central Park, Blackout water, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0525)
    [1] -- John Sex Birthday (part 2), 4/11/1987 [2] -- A Coupla Vixens Talking, 4/12/1987 [3] -- Albert in Central Park, 4/22/1987 [4] -- Blackout water, 5/26/1987
  - Larry Tee and Lahoma arrive from Atlanta, King and Queen of Downtown Pageant Year 2, November 7, 1987 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0526)
  - Candy Store/Quando (end), Va-Va Pyramid, November 14, 1986 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0527)
  - Bentley’s with Trade, October 26, 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0528)
  - Empty Celebrity Club with Trade and Endive, March 16, 1989 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0529)
  - Liberty Hill with Jeanie and Ryan, Columbia with Nancy, February 1989 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0530)
    [1] -- Liberty Hill with Jeanie and Ryan, 2/3/1989 [2] -- Columbia with Nancy, 2/4/1989
  - Zaldi & Cynthia’s house party, Eric Conrad’s roof party, June 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0531)
    [1] -- Zaldi & Cynthia’s house party, 6/12/1988 [2] -- Eric Conrad’s roof party, 6/19/1988
  - Zecca’s Gay Day Concert 1987 with Dean Johnson, Tish, Michael Musto, Zette, Clark, Donna D., etc. (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0532)
  - Jayne County at The World, September 23, 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0533)
  - Atlanta #3, August 1986 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0534)
    [1] -- Atlanta #3, 8/6/1986 [2] -- Atlanta #3, 8/7/1986 [3] -- Atlanta #3, 8/8/1986
  - Pyramid with Va-Va, Michael London, and Queens, John Epperson (Lypsinka) at Pyramid, August 1986 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0535)
    [1] -- Pyramid with Va-Va, Michael London, and Queens, 8/24/1986 [2] -- John Epperson (Lypsinka) at Pyramid, 8/30/1986
  - Albert and Liz at Central Park, April 23, 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0536)
  - Pop Tarts at Pyramid, September 19, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0537)
  - Phyllis Tarter Victorian Concert at YMCA, February 19, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0538)
  - Phyllis Tartar 1 Citicorp, June 14, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0539)
  - Atlanta #1, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0540)
  - 1018 Saturday, January 26, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0541)
  - Dinner with Judy and Margaret Parker, RuPaul show Saturday at Colorbox with The Singing Peek Sisters, February 11, 1989 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0542)
  - San Francisco with James Lambo, Fberuary 16-17, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0543)
  - Gay Day 1987 and Glen Meadmore (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0544)
  - Siberia with People Tree and Phoebe Legere, April 16, 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0545)
  - Now Explosion after Pyramid show: on the street, breakfast, Central Park, May 18, 1986 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0546)
  - Pop Tarts at Limelight (with Kennan and Voltaire), October 1, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0547)
  - Atlanta 1987 #5 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0548)
  - Thanksgiving with The Mustos, November 27, 1986 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0549)
  - Lady Clare and Todd at Pyramid, September 4, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0550)
    Access DVD available by appointment only. Please ask for Part 1 and Part 2.
  - Wigstock IV (part 1), August 31, 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0551)
  - Limelight evening with Michael Musto, Albert, John Moss, First warm day, Backsliders at Nirvana, March 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0552)
    [1] -- Limelight evening with Michael Musto, Albert, John Moss, 3/3/1987 [2] -- First warm day, 3/3/1987 [3] -- Backsliders at Nirvana, 3/9/1987
  - Eric and Vicki at Grams, January 22, 1989 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0553)
  - Last Day In Atlanta, Wendy Wild Benefit, February 12, 1989 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0554)
  - John Sex at Mars, Blackout and I walk to East Village, April 1989 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0555)
    [1] -- John Sex at Mars, 4/23/1989 [2] -- Blackout and I walk to East Village, 4/28/1989
  - Julie Is Her Name at Pyramid (take 2), Lady Bunny (take 2), Julie is Her Name, February 1, 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0556)
    [1] -- Julie Is Her Name at Pyramid (take 2), 2/1/1988 [2] -- Lady Bunny (take 2), 2/3/1988 [3] -- Julie is Her Name, 2/3/1988
  - Gullet without the G (#2), September 19, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0557)
  - Wigstock III (part 3), September 7, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0558)
  - San Francisco #5, February 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0559)
  - Celebrity Club extra end of evening, Mars with International Chrysys, East, Tabboo!, March 1989 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0560)
    [1] -- Celebrity Club extra end of evening, 3/19/1989 [2] -- Mars with International Chrysys, East, Tabboo!, 3/26/1989
  - Nelson at home alone, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0561)
  - Pop Tarts at China Club, June 14, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0562)
  - 1st Celebrity Club at The World, RuPaul Welcome Back Party, 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0563)
  - Sunday inserts, August 9, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0564)
  - Monday inserts, August 10, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0565)
  - Alexis at Green Street, Alexis at La Rocca, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0566)
  - Neon Tetra, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0567)
  - Joshua at Darinka, June 13, 1986 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0568)
  - Brant Mewborn leaves Rolling Stone, Fashion Patrol Birth Show at The World, September 3, 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0569)
  - Backsliders at CBGB’s, June 12, 1986 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0570)
  - New Milk Bar (Kenny), 70’s Tunnel with Floyd, Allison, Lahoma, RuPaul, and Larry Tee, March 31, 1988 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0571)
  - Hawaii Kai party, Kennon (part 2) (see also B-W August 1987), September 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0572)
    [1] -- Hawaii Kai party, 9/2/1987 [2] -- Kennon (part 2) (see also B-W August 1987), 9/10/1987
  - Michael Musto Birthday, Susanne Bartsch New Year's Eve Palladium bash, December 7, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0573)
  - John Sex & Craig Vandenberg at Pyramid, Kill Pig, February 28, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0574)
  - Stephen and Mazima, June 21, 1987 (Box 15, Media ID: 357.0575)
  - Coney Island with Liz, Michael Musto and Albert, June 20, 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0576)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid, East Village evening, Blackout morning walk and East Village evening, June 1986 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0577)
  - Cab ride home, Michael Musto and Albert on Street ("Food Rap"), Pop Tarts at China Club, 5 Ninth Avenue, Eric and Hapi Phace go to Park Opera, June 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0578)
    [1] -- Cab ride home, 6/14/1987 [2] -- Michael Musto and Albert on Street ("Food Rap"), 6/14/1987 [3] -- Pop Tarts at China Club, 6/14/1987 [4] -- 5 Ninth Avenue, 6/15/1987 [5] -- Eric and Hapi Phace go to Park Opera, 6/16/1987
  - Bad Boys, June 20, 1986 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0579)
  - La Palace de Beaute (part 2), October 10, 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0580)
  - Tunnel with French Twist, DeeLite, People Tree, April 7, 1988 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0581)
  - Margaret Parker, Will Brantley, and Stephen Stubbs to Lipstix drag show in Atlanta, Majestic restaurant, February 1989 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0582)
    [1] -- Margaret Parker, Will Brantley, and Stephen Stubbs to Lipstix drag show in Atlanta, 2/9/1989 [2] -- Majestic restaurant, 2/10/1989
  - People Tree at The World, Sauvage at Limelight, December 22, 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0583)
  - Tish and Rhonda to Jane West, June 7, 1986 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0584)
  - Woodstock with Brant, Rhonda and self, August 1988 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0585)
    [1] -- Woodstock with Brant, Rhonda and self, 8/13/1988 [2] -- Woodstock with Brant, Rhonda and self, 8/14/1988
  - House Party & Twilight Zone, Thanksgiving (part 2), 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0586)
    [1] -- House Party & Twilight Zone, 6/19/1987 [2] -- Thanksgiving (part 2), 11/25/1987
  - Backsliders and Cruel Story of Youth at CBGB’s, November 20, 1986 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0587)
  - Atlanta #9: Saturday Mama, August 22, 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0588)
  - Jeanne Beauvais at Cami Hall, October 29, 1988 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0589)
  - (SC) Nancy in Kershaw, Grandmama’s, February 1989 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0590)
    [1] -- (SC) Nancy in Kershaw, 2/2/1989 [2] -- Grandmama’s, 2/3/1989
  - Wigstock Benefit (part 2), CP with Liz, Albert, Michael Musto, Pop Tarts, skyline, fair, May 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0591)
    [1] -- Wigstock Benefit (part 2), 5/13/1987 [2] -- CP with Liz, Albert, Michael Musto, Pop Tarts, skyline, fair, 5/17/1987
  - Flloyd's Chicken Party at Tunnel, December 19, 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0592)
  - Michael Musto’s Dirt #1, Opening night at Private Eyes, September 22, 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0593)
  - East Village including 7A, Wigstock #2 (part 1), 1986 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0594)
    [1] -- East Village including 7A, 8/31/1986 [2] -- Wigstock #2 (part 1), 9/1/1986
  - Wig contest at The World, Slaves Of New York set with Michael Musto and Beauregaurd, Floyd’s party, May 1988 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0595)
    [1] -- Wig contest at The World, 5/10/1988 [2] -- Slaves Of New York set with Michael Musto and Beauregaurd, 5/12/1988 [3] -- Floyd’s party, 5/15/1988
  - Nelson & Nazomi at First on First, Lady Clare (cont), September 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0596)
    [1] -- Nelson & Nazomi at First on First, 9/4/1987 [2] -- Lady Clare (cont), 9/5/1987
  - Boston to Woodstock, Kennon, 1987 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0597)
    [1] -- Boston to Woodstock, 8/1987 [2] -- Kennon, 9/10/1987
  - Changing Of The Guard at Tunnel, Multi Party at Tunnel, March 1988 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0598)
    [1] -- Changing Of The Guard at Tunnel, 3/10/1988 [2] -- Multi Party at Tunnel, 3/12/1988
  - Road trip 88 to Atlanta #1, June 30, 1988 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0599)
  - Nelson Talking, March 5, 1989 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0600)
  - Marrs & then Nelson goes to PYRAMID to see Bunny, January 29, 1989 (Box 16, Media ID: 357.0601)